<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Apple Hot News Ticker</title>
<link>http://altnet.online/hotnews/</link>
<description>Hot News provided by Apple.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Copyright 2007, Apple Inc.</copyright>
<webMaster>rss-feeds@altnet.online</webMaster>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 18:01:16 PDT</pubDate>
<lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 18:01:16 PDT</lastBuildDate>
<category>Apple</category>
<generator>In house</generator>
<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss/</docs>
<item>
<title>“Like a Star Trek Gadget Come to Life”</title>
<link>
http://www.computerworld.com/action/article.do?command=viewArticleBasic&articleId=9026018&pageNumber=1
</link>
<description>
Shortly after activating his new iPhone, Michael DeAgonia (Computerworld.com) received his “ first phone call. A few moments after that, I got another. I was able to swap between calls, merge them, put them on hold, and separate them without hassle. Other phones, of course, do that as well. What’s the difference here? The multitouch screen and interface. I can confirm what early reviewers have already pointed out: it works like magic.” The iPhone, DeAgonia indicates, “ isn’t a collection of features, it’s a well-thought-out multi-function device with functions bound together by a drop-dead simple, drop-dead gorgeous interface. The sum is more than the parts.”
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 17:56:46 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>“It Feels Like You Are Holding the Future”</title>
<link>http://stuff.tv/Review/id-6437/</link>
<description>
“Apple has succeeded in crafting a unique phone that is superior [to] everything else on the market,” remarks Stuff.tv. “In one great leap Apple has rewritten the rules for mobile web browsing, invented a completely new touch-sensitive interface, and evolved the iPod. In the hand, the iPhone oozes sexiness; its wide, high-resolution screen is encircled by a halo of chrome and wrapped on its back side by cool brushed metal. When you hold it, it’s thinner and lighter than pictures would suggest: it feels like you are holding the future.” And Stuff.tv awarded iPhone a five star rating.
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 17:54:30 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>“The best phone that anybody has ever made.”</title>
<link>
http://www.time.com/time/business/article/0,8599,1639068,00.html
</link>
<description>
“Steve Jobs has said, repeatedly, that this is the best iPod that Apple has ever made, and it is. It’s also the best phone that anybody has ever made,” says Lev Gossman. “The user interface,” Grossman marvels, “is crammed with smart little touches — every moment of user interaction has been quietly stage-managed and orchestrated, with such overwhelming attention to detail that when the history of digital interface design is written, whoever managed this project at Apple will be hailed as a Michelangelo, and the iPhone his or her Sistine Chapel.”
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 11:09:11 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
“Apple’s Simple, Versatile iPhone Changes the Game”
</title>
<link>
http://www.sfgate.com/cgi-bin/article.cgi?f=/c/a/2007/06/30/MNGSCQOVMV1.DTL&feed=rss.news
</link>
<description>
“After all the ink that’s been spilled describing, previewing and hyping the Apple iPhone, does it deserve the attention? I’d have to say yes,” reports Ryan Kim (San Francisco Chronicle). “The lure of the iPhone is that it makes you want to use it. It’s actually fun. Do we say that about any phones? Hardly. It’s not really the physical design, which is a marvel of simplicity. It’s what happens when you pick it up and use it. There is nothing intimidating about it. Rather, it’s inviting.” “The cell phone, the most personal of technology devices,” Kim concludes, “has just gotten a whole lot more personal.”
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 11:08:36 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>“A Quantum Leap.”</title>
<link>
http://www.tech.co.uk/gadgets/phones/mobile-phones/features/iphone-making-the-pda-sexy-again?page=2&zoom=
</link>
<description>
“On first inspection, Apple appears to have made a quantum leap in terms of mobile handset usability.” The iPhone, the staff writers at tech.co.uk say, is “making the idea of the PDA sexy again,” offering “an elegant solution for the 21st Century handheld.” Enthusing over the onscreen keyboard, they write that “The iPhone keyboard is ‘intelligent’ in that it prevents and corrects mistyped words, a feature that’s bound to find favor with many. Find out more in our article: Why the iPhone keyboard rocks.”
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 11:06:58 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
iPhone Premieres Friday Night at Apple Retail Stores
</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/iphone/</link>
<description>
This Friday, June 29, at 6:00 pm local time, the revolutionary iPhone goes on sale at the 164 Apple retail stores nationwide, all of which will stay open until midnight. Customers can purchase up to two iPhones on a first-come, first-served basis. Beginning Saturday morning, all Apple retail stores will offer free, in-depth workshops, so customers can learn how to get the most out of their new iPhones. They’ll also have access to free iPhone support at the Genius Bar and personal training through Apple’s new One to One program.
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2007 05:25:52 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>“Amazing,” the iPhone Matches Most of its Hype”</title>
<link>
http://www.nytimes.com/2007/06/27/technology/circuits/27pogue.html
</link>
<description>
“The phone is so sleek and thin,” reports David Pogue (New York Times) in his review of iPhone, that “it makes Treos and Blackberrys look obese.” And the software transcends. “It’s fast, beautiful, menu-free, and dead simple to operate.” If you need “to answer a call, you can tap Answer on the screen, or pinch the microscopic microphone bulge on the white earbud cord. Either way, music or video playback pauses until you hang up.” As for email, it’s “fantastic. Incoming messages are fully formatted, complete with graphics; you can even open (but not edit) Word, Excel and PDF documents.” And “the Web browser,” he points out, “is the real dazzler.” No “stripped down, claustrophobic My First Cellphone Browser; you get full Web layouts, fonts and all, shrunk to fit the screen. You scroll with a fingertip — much faster than scroll bars. You can double-tap to enlarge a block of text for reading, or rotate the screen 90 degrees, which rotates and magnifies the image to fill the wider view.” In short, Pogue calls the iPhone, “the most sophisticated, outlook-changing piece of electronics to come along in years.”
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 19:21:30 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
iPhone a “Beautiful and Breakthrough Handheld Computer”
</title>
<link>http://solution.allthingsd.com/</link>
<description>
After testing the iPhone for two weeks in multiple US cities, Walter Mossberg and Katherine Boehret consider it “a beautiful and breakthrough handheld computer. Its software, especially, sets a new bar for the smart-phone industry, and its clever finger-touch interface,” they say, “works well.” In addition to combining “intelligent voice calling and a full-blown iPod,” iPhone also “offers the best Web browser we have seen on a smart phone and robust email software.” It offers “the largest and highest-resolution screen of any smart phone we’ve seen, and the most internal memory by far. Yet it is one of the thinnest smart phones available and offers impressive battery life, better than its key competitors claim.” It is, the two conclude, “a pleasure to use.”
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 19:19:54 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>“The Most Chic Cellphone I’ve Seen”</title>
<link>
http://www.usatoday.com/tech/columnist/edwardbaig/2007-06-26-iphone-review_N.htm
</link>
<description>
Writing for USA Today, Edward Baig finds iPhone “indeed worth lusting after.” Apple, he says, “has delivered a prodigy—a slender fashion phone, a slick iPod, and an Internet experience unlike any before it on a mobile handset.” “The most chic cellphone I’ve seen,” iPhone is “a breeze to set up and fun to use, evident from the moment you slide your finger across the screen to unlock it. It’s a wonderful widescreen iPod and fabulous picture viewer.” And he tells us that “making calls was surprisingly simple. You can flick through your list of contacts or favorites … and then tap on a name to make a call or send a text message. The keys of the virtual keypad are large enough so that dialing a number manually — or punching in a code to access voice mail remotely — is easy. I rarely made a mistake.” He awards iPhone 3.5 stars out of 4.
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 19:18:57 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
“An Excellent Implementation of State-of-the-art Features”
</title>
<link>
http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/19444948/site/newsweek/page/0/
</link>
<description>
Finding it “a significant leap,” Steven Levy (Newsweek) calls iPhone “a superbly engineered, cleverly designed and imaginatively implemented approach to a problem that no one has cracked to date: merging a phone handset, an Internet navigator and a media player in a package where every component shines, and the features are welcoming rather than foreboding.  The iPhone is the rare convergence device where things actually converge.” iPhone, he says, “finally fulfills the promise of people-friendly palm-top communication and computing.”
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 19:16:43 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>